

# **CONTACTS**

- **L** +375 29 768-80-83
- igors.gudelis@gmail.com
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/igor-gudelis-679855115/
- https://github.com/lgors Gudelis
- s igors.gudelis
- jej igors.gudelis

#### Citizenship:

EU Passport (Republic of Lithuania)

#### **Employment:**

Full time Relocation possible Ready for business trip

## **SKILLS**

- HTML/CSS/SCSS
- Javascript
- Typescript
- Angular 2+
- Angular Material
- RxJS
- Ngrx/Ngxs

# **LANGUAGES**

English



Russian



# **IGOR GUDELIS**

## FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Minsk, Belarus

My CV demo - http://165.22.14.147/ Projects: https://uxcel.com/ https://car4you.by/

#### WORK EXPERIENCE



# Total work experience over 4 years.

03.2020 — Present.

### **Freelance**

Front-End Developer

- Worked in a multilingual team.
- Participated in daily meetings, dev sprint planning, backlog review.
- Implemented designs that work across all modern desktop and mobile browsers.
- Developed features using Serverless on Amazon Web Services.

09.2019 — 03.2020

## CactusSoft

Front-End Developer

- Created project's architecture in line with the latest angular development trends.
- Added Redux-based technologies with the ngxs library which helped improve the application maintainability.
- Was responsible for the whole application's lifecycle from start to the deadline.
- Participated in project team meetings and communicated effectively with business analysts, project managers and QA.

12.2018 — 09.2019

# **VRP Consulting**

Front-End Developer

- Created project's architecture in line with the latest angular development trends.
- Integrated Server-side rendering (SSR) with Angular Universal.
- Managed a team of 2 junior engineers.

11.2016 — 12.2018

#### **Ais Novations**

Front-End Developer

 Took part in creating the official site of the company.

- Developed individually a well structured, maintainable, easy to understand application frontend while adhering to the defined coding standards.
- Participated in daily meetings, identified and resolved gaps in business requirements.

## **EDUCATION**



# Minsk State Architectural and Construction College

economist

#### **COURSES** -



2020

W3Cx, in collaboration with edX.

Front-End Web Developer

https://courses.edx.org/certificates/c8ec0899eede433e9200b7070ad003f2

#### **ABOUT ME** -



Front-end Developer with more than four years of experience in developing new software functionalities and updating existing software.

Work experience in a multilingual team and communication with an English-speaking customer.

Demonstrable ability to learn, adapt, share and integrate knowledge across workgroups.

I can work both in a team and independently,

Self-sufficient in the development of assigned tasks, detailoriented, disciplined, motivated.